<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IEEE MJCET</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cis">CIS</string>
    <string name="cistext1">
        <b>About CIS\n</b>
"CIS focuses on computational intelligence, a collection of biologically and linguistically motivated computational paradigms"
        "including the theory, design, application, and development of neural networks, connectionist systems,"
        "evolutionary algorithms, fuzzy systems, and hybrid intelligent systems.\n\n"
        "The society sponsors various conferences, including the bi-annual IEEE World Congress on Computational Intelligence."
    </string>
    <string name="cistext2">
        <b>"Goals\n"</b>
        "The main goals of CIS under this umbrella are directed towards promoting of the creation of local roots"
        "for our Society in all geographical areas worldwide, the awareness about the activities that we organize,"
        "to identify the members' needs, to create services for them, to recognize the excellence of members and "
        "volunteers, and to develop the overall membership.\n\n"
        "We provide service to our members through a number of programs. We organize social activities in CIS-conferences,"
        "webinar series and summer research grants to students, travel grants to student members presenting papers"
        "at IEEE CIS conferences, as well as to professional members from developing countries. \n"
        "Being a CIS member, you will be able to gain exclusive benefits from these programs: get reduced registration"
        "rates for CIS conferences; opportunity to apply for funding to travel to CIS conferences; participate in summer"
        "schools around the world; apply for research grants; gain access to an academic network of scientists and engineers"
        "working on CI; connect with other members through the social networks and get informed on job positions; connect with"
        "local industries and recent graduates; get tips on publishing at CIS journals and participate in CIS webinars.\n"

    </string>
    <string name="cistext3">
        "<b>Website:</b>"
            "\n http://www.ieee-cis.org"
    </string>
    <string name="icstext1">
        <b>Vision</b>
        "\n To be the leading provider of technical information, community services, and personalized services to the world's"
        "computing professionals."
    </string>
    <string name="icstext2">
       <b>Goal</b>
        "\nBe essential to the global technical community and computer professionals everywhere and be universally"
        "recognized for the contributions of technical professionals in developing and applying technology to improve"
        "global conditions."

    </string>
    <string name="icstext3">
       <b>About ICS</b>
        "\n The IEEE Computer Society is the world's leading membership organization dedicated to computer science"
        "and technology. Serving more than 60,000 members, the IEEE Computer Society is the trusted information,"
        "networking, and career-development source for a global community of technology leaders that includes researchers,"
        "educators, software engineers, IT professionals, employers, and students.\n\n"
        "The IEEE Computer Society sponsors more than 200 technical conferences and events each year, including the"
        "industry-oriented "Rock Stars" series, all over the world, aimed at research and industry professionals."
        "Our publications are peer-reviewed, indexed, and authored by technology thought leaders worldwide,"
        "and include 17 scholarly journals and 13 magazines featuring the latest technology trends.\n"
        "We also offer cutting-edge products such as the myComputer app (available for iOS or Android),"
        "that provide unprecedented user-driven access to our content, and our Digital Library with more"
        "than 550,000 articles and papers spanning the full spectrum of computer science and technology.\n"

    </string>
    <string name="icstext4">
       <b>Website:\n</b>
        "https://www.computer.org/"

    </string>
    <string name="pestext1">
        <b>Mission</b>
        "\nTo be the leading provider of scientific and engineering information on electric power and energy"
        "for the betterment of society, and the preferred professional development source for our members"
        "~ Approved by the IEEE PES Governing Board, 17 July 2003."
    </string>
    <string name="pestext2">
        <b>About PES</b>
        "\n The Power and Energy Society (PES) provides the world's largest forum for sharing the latest"
        "in technological developments in the electric power industry, for developing standards that guide"
        "the development and construction of equipment and systems, and for educating members of the industry"
        "and the general public. Members of the Power and Energy Society are leaders in this field, and they —"
        "and their employers — derive substantial benefits from involvement with this unique and outstanding association."

    </string>
    <string name="pestext3">
        <b>PES Field of Interest</b>
        "\nThe scope of the Society embraces research, development, planning, design, construction,"
        "maintenance, installation and operation of  equipment, structures, materials and power systems"
        "for the safe, sustainable, economic and reliable conversion, generation, transmission, distribution,"
        "storage and usage of electric energy, including its measurement and control."
    </string>
    <string name="pestext4">
       <b>"Website:"</b>
        "\n http://www.ieee-pes.org/"
    </string>
    <string name="castext1">
        <b>Mission</b>
        "\n Our mission is to foster CASS members across disciplines to address humanity’s grand challenges"
        "by conceiving and pioneering solutions to fundamental and applied problems in circuits and systems."
    </string>
    <string name="castext2">
        <b>Vision</b>
        "\n The IEEE Circuits and Systems Society (CASS) believe that the Grand Engineering Challenges"
        "of the 21st century can only be addressed in an inter-disciplinary and cross-disciplinary manner."
        "The Society’s unique and profound expertise in Circuits, Systems, Signals, Modeling, Analysis, and"
        "Design can have a decisive impact on important issues such as Sustainable Energy, Bio-Health, Green"
        "Information Technology, Nano-Technology, and Scalable Information Technology Systems."
    </string>
    <string name="castext3">
        <b>About CASS</b>
        "\n The IEEE Circuits and Systems Society is the leading organization that promotes the advancement of the"
        "theory, analysis, design, tools, and implementation of circuits and systems. The field spans their theoretical"
        "foundations, applications, and architectures, as well as circuits and systems implementation of algorithms for"
        "signal and information processing."
        "\n The Society brings engineers, researchers, scientists and others involved in circuits and systems applications access"
        "to the industry’s most essential technical information, networking opportunities, career development tools and"
        "many other exclusive benefits."
        "\n Local members with similar technical interests engage in professional exchange through the Society’s 10 regional chapters"
        "in the United States, Canada, Europe, the Middle East, Africa, Latin America, Asia, Australia and the Pacific."
    </string>
    <string name="castext4">
        <b>Website:</b>
        "\n http://ieee-cas.org/"
    </string>
    <string name="wietext1">
        <b>Mission and Vision</b>
        "\n\n Our goal is to facilitate the recruitment and retention of women in technical disciplines globally."
        "We envision a vibrant community of IEEE women and men collectively using their diverse talents to innovate"
        "for the benefit of humanity."
        "\n\n IEEE WIE strives to…"
     "\n\n• Recognize the outstanding achievements of women in electrical and electronics engineering through IEEE Awards nominations."
     "\n\n• Organize receptions at major technical conferences to enhance networking and to promote membership in WIE."
     "\n\n• Advocate women in leadership roles in IEEE governance, and career advancement for women in the profession."
     "\n\n• Provide assistance with the formation of new WIE Affinity Groups, and support ongoing activities."
     "\n\n• Promote IEEE member grade advancement for women to the membership grades of Senior member and Fellow."
     "\n\n• Facilitate the development of programs and activities that promote the entry into, and retention of, women in engineering programs."
     "\n\n• Administer the IEEE Student-Teacher and Research Engineer/Scientist (STAR) Program to mentor young women in junior and high schools."
    </string>
    <string name="wietext2">
        <b>About WIE</b>
        "\n IEEE Women in Engineering (WIE) is one of the largest international professional organizations dedicated"
        "to promoting women engineers and scientists, and inspiring girls around the world to follow their academic"
        "interests in a career in engineering."
    </string>
    <string name="wietext3">
        <b>Website:</b>
        "\n http://wie.ieee.org/"
    </string>
    <string name="hometext1">
      "IEEE Student Branch MJCET has been the frontrunner in providing quality technical education under the able"
      "guidance of  Dr. Kaleem Fatima (Former Branch Counselor  IEEE  MJCET)  Mr.  Arifuddin  Sohel  (Former Branch"
      "Mentor  IEEE MJCET and current branch counsellor), Mrs. Maniza Hijab (Chapter Advisor IEEE CIS MJCET) and Mrs. Ajaz"
      "Fatima (Chapter Advisor IEEE PES MJCET).It was established in the year 2002 with an aim of making the students of"
      "MJCET technically sound and to encourage students to prove their mettle."
      "\n\nThe  student  branch  has  been  exploring  new  domains  in  the  fields  of industry and academia relationships with"
      "the support from the IEEE Hyderabad Section. The student branch has started new chapters like the IEEE Computational"
      "Intelligence Society(CIS), IEEE Computer Society (ICS), IEEE Circuits and Systems(CASS), Women In Engineering Affinity"
      "Group (WIE) for the student community to excel besides the IEEE Power and Energy Society (PES)."
     "\n\nIEEE MJCET has very good bonding with Hyderabad section since its inception and has regularly conducted events in"
      "collaboration with section. The student branch has recently held HAMFEST INDIA 2014 which was organized by LARC and"
      "IEEE HYD section."
  </string>
    <string name="hometext2">
        <b>IEEE MJCET- At a Glance</b>
"\n\n• IEEE MJCET SB is one of the most vibrant student branch of Hyderabad section and has recently won the award for"
        “MOST VIBRANT SB” at SSC 2014. The student branch has won the award previously in the year 2011."
"\n• In the same  year  our Branch Counselor Dr. Kaleem Fatima was conferred the title of ‘Outstanding Branch Counselor’
        in the entire R10– region."
"\n• In 2012, IEEE Student Branch MJCET was recognized as one of ‘the Innovative and Best Practices Student Branch’
        by the IEEE Hyderabad Section."
"\n• IEEE Student Branch MJCET crossed a milestone when its member-strength crossed the 200 mark and is currently
        grooming about 220 potential students. With this,our IEEE-MJCET becomes one of the two/three
        student branches in the entire state to hold this distinguished record of a massive
        IEEE member-driven student organization comprising of varied talents and potentials."
    </string>
    <string name="hometext3">
        <b>Official Websites:</b>
        "\nhttps://www.ieee.org/"
        "\nhttp://www.ieeehyd.org/"
        "\nhttps://www.ieeefoundation.org/"

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_cis_card">cis_card</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ics_card">ics_card</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pes_card">pes_card</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cas_card">cas_card</string>
    <string name="title_activity_wie_card">wie_card</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login2">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_aaa">aaa</string>
</resources>
